const Quiz = [
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for the main method in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "public static void Main(String[] args)",
            "private void main(String[] args)",
            "public void main(String[] args)",
            "public static void main(String[] args)"
        ],
        "ans": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these data types is used to create a variable that should store text?",
        "answers": [
            "int",
            "float",
            "String",
            "boolean",
        ],
        "ans": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which method can be used to find the length of a string in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "length()",
            "getSize()",
            "lengthof()",
            "getLength()",
        ],
        "ans": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to define a class in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "define",
            "create",
            "class",
            "classType"
        ],
        "ans": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the size of an int variable in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "2 bytes",
            "4 bytes",
            "8 bytes",
            "1 byte"
        ],
        "ans": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a Java keyword?",
        "answers": [
            "new",
            "class",
            "if",
            "then"
        ],
        "ans": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these access specifiers can be used for a class so that it can be accessed by classes inside the same package?",
        "answers": [
            "public",
            "default",
            "private",
            "protected",
        ],
        "ans": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which method must be defined by a Java class that implements the java.lang.Runnable interface?",
        "answers": [
            "execute()",
            "start()",
            "launch()",
            "run()"
        ],
        "ans": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "0",
            "null"
        ],
        "ans": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these operators is used to allocate memory to an object?",
        "answers": [
            "malloc",
            "alloc",
            "new",
            "create"
        ],
        "ans": 2
    }
]



export default Quiz;
